♪ Playing with fire ♪
♪ I should have learned ♪
♪ Somebody's gonna get burned  ♪
♪ We got bad... bad blood ♪
Where did we go?
-Oh, babe. You know, everywhere.
-Dubai, Maldives...
One way ticket to everywhere.
-ABC: Always Be Closing.
-[Jason] We have to.
[Christine] I wanna say hi to Mary.
[Christine] Hi, babe!
[Mary] Christine had a lot to say about
how quickly Romain and I got engaged.
Hi, nice to finally meet you.
I don't know how long they were really
dating before she got engaged,
but it's like a fraction of the time.
-Cheers!
-[Christine] Cheers.
I don't necessarily have anything
to say to Christine
and I'm hoping Christine feels the same.
I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm hiding out.
So, have you seen Chrishell
since you got here?
-Sorry, I'm gonna get a drink.
-Okay.
Like, she's acting weird?
[Davina] She didn't wanna hang,
so I don't know, She just walked away.
[Chrishell] Can I get a vodka on the rocks
with lemon, please?
[Chrishell] Thank you.
[Maya] But I love Miami.
You know I love LA, too.
I know the LA market better
because I've been here 15 years
and I did real estate here
for six years, so...
[Jason] Nothing wrong with getting
a high unsolicited offer.
Even if they're not interested yet,
you never know.
[Chrishell] Look at all the houses
we could sell!
-[Heather] I know. In time.
-[Chrishell laughing]
So, you weren't there that day
we were in the office.
I feel like Brett and Jason
were starting to give me
shit again about my relationship.
Oh, no.
Brett's one to talk. He invited
seven girls here tonight to meet him
at the same party.
[Heather] I know.
That's why I'm like, "Brett, please.
Don't-- Don't even start in on me
right now.
-Like honestly, don't start in."
-Hi, ladies!
[Heather] Hi.
-Hey.
-[Heather] How are you? Come sit.
Can I have a moment with Chrishell
if you don't mind?
Yes. Are you guys good? Are you sure?
I just haven't seen her.
-[Heather] Okay, okay.
-[Christine] Thank you!
[Heather] Alright, ladies.
Play nice, please.
[Heather chuckles] Love you girls.
I just wanted to come by
and say hi and catch up.
[both chuckling]
What's going on?
Nothing much. Just got back
and ready to get back to work.
And I know I haven't seen you in like...
I don't know how long it's been.
-Yeah, it's been a long time.
-I know.
I don't want there to be, like,
this tension and this awkwardness, like...
I don't want you to walk into a room
and, you know, like, just avoid me.
I don't want that anymore.
I can be cordial with anybody,
so it's totally fine.
-Yeah.
-[Chrishell] I feel like we could, like,
-have a truce...
-Yeah.
...and agree to coexist.
You know, we don't have to braid
each other's hair.
The thing is, like,
I don't want to coexist, you know?
I wanna be friends again.
There's action.
I don't if they're gonna...
I'm good not being friends with you.
It's been a very toxic...
relationship, having you in my life
and so many times
you've brought toxic energy to me.
And so I don't want anything
to do with that.
Are you saying you will not give me
a chance to be your friend?
It looks like it's going well.
[Romain] One of them
is gonna finish in the pool.
No, I think actually...
-[Mary] I've seen...
-I have a good feeling.
Let's get a bet.
Who do you bet on?
Every time I deal with you,
you do something insanely,
ridiculously hurtful.
Like telling all the girls
not to like my Instagrams,
like, when you had a party
and you made fun of me on the drink list
to hundreds of your guests.
She named the drink,
"The Two Faced Chrishell."
Okay, you know what, actually it's
"Chrishell's Two Faced Tonic." I'm sorry.
You know, I actually do have
two faces for her, I have to say,
because I don't like her, so...
I'm trying to be professional
and so, this is probably
the face that I give her.
Do I look dead behind the eyes?
-You didn't mean to hurt my feelings?
-You had a party and didn't invite me.
I didn't have a party prior.
-You didn't invite me to your party.
-Christine.
We had parties on the same night.
But I didn't put your face
on my drink list
and make fun of you to all my guests.
It's-- To me, it's insane you could
do all this crazy behavior and then
sit here and act like nothing happened.
This is my olive branch.
I've reached out many times.
You moved into your new house,
and your dog...
I sent you flowers
and I just-- I heard nothing from you.
Wait, Christine. My dog?
You sent me flowers? No. You sent me
flowers when my dad passed.
Christine has this special way
of making everything about her
and this is the perfect example.
And I was dealing with the coroner,
and all of a sudden
Jason and Davina are calling me,
saying you're flipping out because
I didn't say thank you for flowers.
But I wasn't home and I didn't get them.
Okay.
I am so sorry from the bottom of my heart.
Give me one more chance...
to not be a fucking bitch.
I love and respect you from
the bottom of my heart. I really do.
It would be really nice
to walk into a room
and have her not run away from me.
[chuckles]
I have ex-boyfriends for that, please.
Like, I have plenty of people running away
from me, I don't need one more.
That's very sweet. Thank you.
I do appreciate the apology.
It's more than I was expecting.
[Chrishell] What do they say,
"Keep your friends close,
keep your enemies closer"?
Hey, babe. How's it going?
That's never been truer
than with Christine.
-Hi, how are you? I'm Chrishell.
-Hi.
-Christian, nice to meet you.
-Oh, sorry, you guys haven't met.
No.
-Congratulations.
-Oh, thanks.
-I'm a lucky man. [chuckles]
-Yeah.
I've definitely learned how
to keep my guard up with her.
I'll leave you love birds.
She's taught me how to work
in an environment where
I zip myself into my little...
[chuckles] bubble of
"Leave me the fuck alone."
♪ Hard
Steady on the block ♪
♪ Steady on the block
♪I'm burning up, I go hard ♪
♪ Steady on the block... ♪
-[Christine] Rude driver.
-I don't think you can pull up here.
-[horn beeps]
-Oh, shut up!
-[car horn beeping]
-Fuck off! Go around me.
They can suck my dick, these drivers.
[Davina mumbles]
-I can't wait for you to see this.
-Oh, my gosh, I'm so excited.
Oh, my God, this is so funny
that this is the house.
I drive past this house all the time.
-Do you really?
-[Christine] No, I'm serious.
This is the coolest house ever.
I always wondered what is was.
-[Davina] I'm excited for you to see this.
-Oh, my God. I can't wait to see this.
This is sick, Davina!
-I know, I'm so excited.
-God, call the doctor, this is sick!
[Christine] This is just like heaven.
[Davina] How amazing would it be
if I could get this listing?
-Incredible.
-I mean, you fit perfectly.
-So...
-I've never seen anything like it.
[Christine] This is so my vibe.
What's the lot size?
[Davina] It's over an acre,
it's around 16,000 square feet,
-and there's this amazing guest house.
-Oh, my gosh. Wow.
Davina's client is a real estate mogul.
And this is a make-or-break deal.
We're talking about
a million dollar commission here.
How did you meet him?
Yeah, so I sold him two condos,
I wanna say three or four years ago.
We, you know, established a relationship
through working together
and he's fabulous.
Well, I'm dying to see more.
You have to show me my kitchen.
I mean, the kitchen.
[both laughing]
[Christine] Honestly, this is
the most fabulous kitchen
I have ever seen in any home,
and I'm not just saying that.
It's so warm and modern.
I wanna know what you think it's worth.
The client was thinking somewhere
around 100 million, 80 million.
Somewhere around there.
It's a lot of money. Yeah.
It's a lot of money.
It's difficult to comp
a property of this size.
I mean not only is it sitting on
an acre of land in Beverly Hills,
but it's very, very specific and stylized,
so it's not something people are buying
and selling everyday, that's for sure.
Here's my opinion on the house.
So, this house is fabulous.
I would live here in a heartbeat.
However, it is very stylized.
There's no view, it's in Beverly Hills
off of Coldwater Canyon
and it's a very loud and busy road.
-That's my only concern.
-Yeah.
However, that aside...
it's a great house on an acre of land.
I would say 70.
Yeah, I was thinking around 70 as well
because we're in Beverly Hills.
Right here, too. I mean, it couldn't...
You're like, literally,
you're in Rodeo Drive in five minutes.
This is just so great.
There are international buyers
that love Beverly Hills,
and they want a compound
'cause they have big families.
Just because it's listed
at a certain price,
it doesn't mean
it's going to sell for that price.
Show me the master bedroom,
I have to see this.
[Davina] I've worked really hard.
I've known this client for five years.
So, like...
[Christine] Oh, the sparkles in the sky!
[Christine gasps]
[Davina] Yeah, it's a famous chandelier.
I love the privacy
and the compound feel.
-[Christine] This is billionaire status.
-[Davina] I know, exactly.
Billionaires have compounds,
millionaires have views.
[Davina] I would agree.
-[Davina] Oh, my God.
-[Christine] This is gorgeous.
[Davina] I know. It just took
my breath away just looking at it.
-[Christine] This is just so fabulous.
-It's just idyllic.
Christine, I have to make this work.
-Oh, my God.
-I know.
We need to resort it.
Get the feeling, get the atmosphere.
[Christine] Okay, so what would you do...
if Jason chose to not take the listing?
I mean, I would try to talk
some sense into him.
Because Jason owns the brokerage,
he has the right to refuse any property.
I think Davina is gonna have a hard time
getting it listed at this price.
I have to try, and I hope
Jason is on board, you know?
-Hopefully...
-[Christine] And if he's not?
If he pushes me against the wall
and doesn't allow me the opportunity,
then I might have to just do my own thing
and take the listing.
As a real estate agent, you have to be
underneath a broker, it's required,
but I have my broker's license,
so in theory,
I could go do my own thing
and have my own company
and not have to listen to anyone,
including Jason.
[Christine] I don't blame you.
-What would you do?
-I'd do the same thing. Bon voyage, Jason!
See ya, wouldn't want to be ya!
I hope he doesn't make me do that.
I mean, well, this is a bigger listing
than he has, so...
I think Jason could potentially be jealous
of Davina's 80 million dollar house.
I mean, at the end of the day,
the biggest listing he's ever had is 40,
and if she closes or even comes close
to getting an 80 million dollar listing,
that's a big deal.
♪ Like a boss, boss, boss ♪
♪ I'm the one walking in my shoes ♪
♪ I'm the one making all these moves ♪
♪ I say when, I say where, I say who ♪
♪ Just like a boss, boss, boss ♪
♪ I got this
You can't stop this ♪
♪ Yeah, I make them go ♪
♪ When I do it like I do ♪
♪ 'Cause I got this ♪
♪ Yeah, I rock this ♪
♪ Any way I wanna do it
I'mma do it like a boss ♪
[Chrishell] There is a lot of opportunity
in the Valley,
but these homes do come with
a separate group of challenges.
You're losing your prestigious zip code,
and with this specific house,
it's really loud because of the highway.
[Maya] You ready to see this house, Aiden?
My clients are growing up,
they get married,
they don't want to live
in the bachelor pad in the Hills.
So, you go to the 'burbs.
I'm excited to explore the Valley
and see what that market offers to them.
-[Chrishell] Oh, my God!
-I wanna look cute doing this,
but this stroller is actually really heavy
so I actually need your help.
-[Aiden crys]
-No. Let me help you.
How do you do this if I'm not here?
[Maya] I'll tell you how, I'm getting
herniated discs everywhere,
osteothorisis, osteoporisis,
whatever you call this.
-[Chrishell] Oh, my God, this is no joke.
-It's really heavy.
-[Chrishell] Hi!
-This is Aiden.
-Hi!
-Hi, first of all. [laughing]
Hi, how are you?
This is cute, Chrishell. I like it.
[Chrishell] Isn't it so pretty?
-Look at those beams.
-I know.
I'm sorry, this takes precedence
over the beams.
-Hi!
-[Maya laughing]
-Oh, he's smiling at me!
-He's smiling at you. He's so cute.
-[Maya] Chrishell, if he spits on you...
-Oh, can I hold you?
Oh. It'll be my fault, I asked for it.
[Chrishell] I hope people come in
while he's here
because I feel like this helps
show it's a family...
-Yeah, a family place.
-...residential place.
[Maya] So yeah, show me the house.
I wanna tell my client a bit about it.
[Chrishell] Okay.
Let's see the kitchen! You wanna see it?
[Maya] So, this is cute, Chrishell.
So he flipped it, he bought it as a fixer
and just put money in this thing?
-Yes. Oh, no, sorry about that.
-That's okay.
[Chrishell] Um, yeah,
so it's all new bones.
Sorry, old bones, but new inside.
You see he did like a mix.
I feel like he did a good job
of keeping the feel,
-but like the modern cabinets...
-Yeah.
[Maya] I love it. It's so bright
and the ceilings are nice and high.
[Chrishell] Look at this. Aw.
[Maya] I don't mind bringing him to
showings, it could work sometimes.
[Chrishell] He's an angel child.
He hasn't cried once.
-I wanna show you outside real quick.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-I have a nice selling point.
The 20 minutes
that I can actually do things.
-He's sleeping.
-I know.
[Maya] This is a perfect family house.
With a backyard and it's pretty quiet,
kind of.
[Maya] Wait.
[cars humming]
I'm listening.
What? Oh, the freeway?
No, don't listen.
They need to add a waterfall
and it'll be fine.
This is like an original 19... Oh, my!
-My heels...
-You're sinking in the grass.
See? That's why I'm wearing thick heels.
[Maya] I like the Sutton house.
But let me tell you, the 405
is one of the busiest freeways in LA.
It takes you from the Valley
all the way to LAX
and all the way south to Orange County,
so there is always activity.
It doesn't matter if it's Friday,
Sunday, it's midnight...
The event last night
was pretty fun, huh? Like...
It was eventful.
-I thought...
-Why?
I don't know, there was something
different about the way
that Christine was apologizing,
as opposed to the other apologies.
I felt like they were very surface.
You think it's because maybe she's engaged
and now maybe her mindset
is a little different and she's, like--
I don't know if that's the case
and I don't know if this is for real,
but I'm taking it with a grain of salt.
I don't want to be that idiot
that's like, "Sure."
You know? And then it happens again?
You know, I think time will-- will help.
By the way you look good
with the stroller, holding the baby.
I know people probably
ask you all the time,
"When are you gonna have a baby?"
-Oh, my God. I get asked everyday.
-Annoying, right?
I just feel like it's a private thing,
so I'll say, "Oh, we don't know yet."
But they'll be like,
"Well, how old are you?"
-I'm like, "Ugh..."
-Yeah.
People actually ask me how old I am
and it's insulting.
You don't have to do something
just because
people tell you that's what
you're supposed to do.
Make sure it's right for you.
At this point, you know, we haven't
decided what's right for us yet.
I could totally see myself diving
into that life and doing that,
and then I also...
Run for your hills! I'm kidding.
-No, run for the hills?
-[Chrishell laughing]
Run for the hills.
-Run! "Run, Forrest, run."
-Your sayings are my favorites.
♪ Call it what you want ♪
♪ But I make my own way ♪
♪ Everybody keeps looking ♪
-Hello.
-[Mary] Hi, Lizzie?
-Yes.
-Hi, Mary.
-Nice to meet you. Come in.
-Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
When you go on a listing appointment,
you go in there
basically selling yourself and selling
what you can do.
It's kind of like a job interview.
Every agent in town is fighting
to get a listing like this
and I have to make the best impression.
I'm so glad that my friend Elliot
got me in touch with you guys.
Can you give me a tour?
-I'm happy to.
-Cool.
[Mary] So the kitchen
obviously is ridiculously stunning.
[Lizzie] Thank you.
-This was originally four rooms.
-Okay.
That was just the kitchen
on the back wall.
This was the breakfast nook,
bar and storage.
So I blew out all four rooms
and created one big open space.
[Mary] So much better.
And then, it's five bedrooms.
-[Mary] Correct?
-Yes.
[Mary] Okay.
The guest house, is that...
[Lizzie] That's counted
in the five bedrooms.
-[Mary] And it's permitted, or not?
-Yes.
-Perfect.
-Something we did in the renovation.
Perfect. That helps with the home value.
Okay, this is really pretty.
I love that chandelier.
[Lizzie] Thank you.
-[Mary] We're kind of matching.
-[Lizzie] I noticed that too. [laughing]
[Mary] Alright, well, we both have
the same taste on something at least.
[Mary] Okay, so formal living room
and the little family room over there.
I love all of these details.
It looks like you spent a lot of time.
I love this house.
It is so gorgeous. It is my dream home.
It was previously listed
with a baller agent.
And if I fight off the competition,
I get the listing,
it's going to take me
to a whole other level.
As a brokerage, what we do is
an extensive amount of marketing.
This is the Oppenheim Group magazine.
So for every listing, they will get in
and your home will be in that.
We do it on the front of the MLS magazine.
We never do the small pictures,
we do full-page ads.
So, it's impossible for any agent
to not see your home.
-Great.
-[Mary laughing]
[Mary] These are all of the homes
we've sold here in the Hills.
-Wow.
-This is our niche.
[Lizzie] The main thing we're looking for
is someone who really cares
about this house
because it's very different
and we want it to be treated differently.
Do you have an idea on home value
or do you want me to give
my opinion on it?
-[Lizzie] Um...
-Which I will anyway, but...
That's a good question. Home value?
I'd love to hear your opinion.
It is a very special home.
You've got the flat lot,
the privacy and the Bird Streets.
But homes in the Hills, people want views.
That's the downside on this one,
it doesn't have a view.
So I would not go above $9,750,000.
We just have a lot of money in the house
since we renovated
and put love into the renovation, so...
I think it's very special
when the agent and brokerage
recognizes and appreciates
the details of the home
because that excitement, that passion
is going to come through to the buyer.
Totally agree.
It's important to have someone passionate.
I got to tell you, I am. [laughing]
This is my dream home.
I'm getting married
in just a couple of months, so,
you know, I'm always looking for homes.
I gotta say, this is my dream home.
Thank you. Congrats on getting married,
that's exciting.
Thank you.
I have a few more meetings with some
other agents and then we'll be in touch.
I look forward to hearing
back from you soon.
Yeah, we'll talk soon.
-Perfect.
-Nice to meet you.
♪ Breaking through the ceiling ♪
♪ Shattered through the roof ♪
[knocking on door]
♪ Taking what I'm feeling ♪
♪ Show them how I do ♪
♪ I've got the goal ♪
-Hi, babe.
-How are you? Hello.
Wow.
-I'm so glad you're finally seeing it.
-Gorgeous.
[Heather] How are you? Wow.
Brett, it's beautiful.
[Brett] Thank you.
Well, it took two months, but yeah,
I just moved in.
[Heather] It feels like home.
[Heather] Mmm.
This is how I keep an eye on you girls.
-I can see all the homes in the Hills.
-Oh my gosh.
[Heather] Wow.
Brett, it's so beautiful.
-Have you brought any girls back here yet?
-[both laughing]
-All right, fine, yes.
-[Heather laughing]
They weren't sleeping
in my room, were they?
-[chuckles] Which one is yours?
-I don't know. Show me.
-Yeah, I'll show you some rooms.
-Wow.
It's really beautiful.
-[Brett] The master.
-[Heather] Sexy!
Right?
-[gasps] I love it.
-Isn't that cool?
[Brett] Boom!
[Heather] Wow.
I love the see-through shower.
And a bathtub.
I finally have a bathtub.
I've never taken a bath in there.
-You have to.
-I know. I know.
-[Heather] Baths are so relaxing.
-I've got bath salts.
I just haven't done it.
So, how many rooms total?
Three bedrooms, four bathrooms.
-Four bathrooms here?
-Yeah.
[Brett] Everything is voice-activated.
Wait, so what do you do?
"Hallway light off?"
[Brett] Little codes.
I'm not gonna tell you
because you'll screw it up.
[Heather] I'm not gonna...
I won't screw anything up.
-[Brett] You will.
-So, is this is my room?
[Brett] Check this out.
A map of LA from 100 years ago.
Oh, wow.
Brett, this place is huge.
It's so unexpected.
When I think of condos,
I don't think of something this big.
[Brett] It's almost too big for me, but...
-Well? Hello!
-[Brett laughing]
[Heather] Now Tarek, though.
Do you want Tarek and me living here?
[Brett] Yeah, that'd be awesome.
It's my dream come true.
-Let's sit down.
-So beautiful.
So, do you sit and watch the sunsets
at night alone?
[Brett] Um... No.
-No?
-No.
Don't you get lonely
being here by yourself?
You know, I'm pretty good being
by myself. It's weird, you know?
Do you ever envision
yourself getting married?
[scoffs] Yeah... I mean, no.
But I know one day I'll meet a woman
and five days later...
my answer will be different.
-Okay, so tell me honestly.
-Okay.
If we started dating five years ago,
where do you think we'd be?
-Divorced.
-Divorced?
[laughing] Oh, my God.
Brett and I have never dated.
But I think we've bonded on a deeper level
just 'cause we've spent a lot
of one-on-one time together.
[Brett] The truth is,
if we were on the same page,
I'd have a mad crush on you,
but we're on different pages so who cares.
-That's the truth.
-We want very different things.
Our bond is so strong.
You're probably one
of my best guy friends.
I'm glad you feel that way.
-You're in a good place, right?
-[Heather chuckles]
-Yeah, I'm good.
-You're, like, with a good man.
-You're gonna give me shit?
-A little bit. You're never as fun
when you're in a relationship
as you are when you're single.
-When you're single, you're fun.
-I know.
I'm glad you're happy, though. Sounds like
you're really doing well with this guy.
Yeah, it's long distance
and I'm in Orange County,
so it's back and forth,
which takes my mind out of work.
-Yeah, I've noticed a little bit.
-It's new, so I think once we're...
Get through the puppy dog phase?
I hope that never goes away.
-But...
-I hope it does.
Get your ass back to work.
I know, but yeah.
I need to enjoy this moment
-and then I can focus.
-That's cool.
-What? Tell me.
-No, I'll buy that.
What are your concerns?
My concern is that last time
you were in a relationship,
you kind of started
screwing up a little bit.
I expect you to be operating at an
incredible level because I know you can.
Sometimes you're not and it's usually
'cause a man is involved. That's all.
It's hard to balance this now
with his kids, too.
I'm like playing...
-You're kinda playing Mom a little bit.
-I'm Mom, yeah.
He went through, like, a huge divorce
and never thought he'd marry again
and never thought he'd fall in love again,
then he met me.
-So... And like, everything changed.
-Yeah.
Anything that makes you happy
makes me happy.
Unless it screws around with your career.
Maya has a freaking baby and she's
doing it, so you can do it with a man.
I just don't like when people
question my relationship.
I feel very judged,
and I'm very protective of my relationship,
and I'm very protective of those children
that are now in my life.
-My expectations for you are high.
-Mm-hmm.
And so anything less than that
pisses me off.
♪ All the little haters on Hater Street ♪
♪ Know I got the kind of rhythm
That can rock that beat ♪
♪ Fire! In my veins ♪
♪ Thunder! Feel me shake ♪
♪ Get ready, I'm a woman
I don't need no favors ♪
♪ You should have seen me coming
I'm a force of nature ♪
♪ Get ready, I'm a force of nature ♪
♪ I'm a force of nature ♪
[telephone ringing]
Hey, babe.
[Jason] Hey, guess what we just got
in my email?
-[Mary] What?
-The listing agreement signed for Doheny.
[gasps, laughs excitedly]
[Mary] Oh my God, it's signed?
[Jason] He just signed it.
[Mary] That is so exciting. 9.7, right?
[Jason] 9.75 million, yeah.
-We just got it signed.
-[Mary] Boom!
Oh, my God, I can't wait.
I'll come down, we'll celebrate.
-[Jason] I'll be in the office.
-Yay! Okay.
[Amanza] Honey, I'm home.
[Mary] Babe!
Hi.
You won't believe what just happened.
[Amanza] What?
I just got that 10 million dollar
listing on Doheny.
Shut up.
Jason just called me.
Oh, God, that gives me goosebumps.
[Mary] Eee!
Good job, mama.
I know, I'm so excited!
Can you help me drag this dead body
in here? It's really heavy.
Thank you.
[Amanza] I wanted to add
some life to the place.
-[Mary] What'd you bring?
-A dead body. I'm kidding.
I've been designing--
Doing interior design
for about seven years.
It's a natural gift that I've always had,
and it came from
growing up really poor.
I lived in a trailer.
I would get like one can of paint a year,
and I would paint everything in my room,
from, like, the bunk beds,
to the dresser, to the accessories.
I got really creative.
I became a DIY master,
like, at a very young age.
-These are cute.
-Okay.
-[Mary] Where do you want them?
-You can sit those there.
I'm gonna put the other one over here.
Somehow, it just worked out.
I got one client here
and one client there,
and built a resume and then was able to do
what I absolutely love
and become this mama interior decorator.
[Amanza] This is what I do
after every staging job.
I just take a nap.
[Mary] Oh, do you?
And I wake up awkwardly
when people come in, like, "Oh, sorry!"
[Amanza] And now that I'm an agent,
I can list the house, stage the house,
sell the house, then decorate the house.
So it's like, cha-ching, cha-ching,
and mama and babies win.
I have something to run by you.
[Mary] Um...
So, Romain and I were looking
at wedding venues
and we were talking about taking
the wedding list down even more.
And he was like, well, I know one person
that's not gonna be on the list,
Davina.
-And I was like, "What?"
-What?
"Davina." I was like, "Why?"
He said because she's disrespectful,
she's negative and...
he does not want to be
sitting there worried about
her having negative responses.
"Oh, this is the food they have?
Oh, this is it?
Oh, this is where they chose
to get married?"
Yeah, I'm like... And so...
I think he just thought,
"Why do you always look at the bad side?"
-Does she even realize she's doing it?
-I don't know.
He has to sit her down and just tell her.
I told him he's gonna tell her.
I'm not frickin' telling her.
-Aw, I feel so bad for you.
-I know!
[Amanza] Fuck!
[Mary] This is my fucking nightmare.
I think Romain's decision to not have
Davina at the wedding is valid.
When he proposed to Mary,
he didn't have the money for
a real diamond ring at the time,
so he proposed with a moissanite,
and Davina made fun of it
and totally emasculated him.
So... you make your bed, you lie in it.
-[Amanza] I mean...
-Hmm...
I feel like my blood pressure
is going high!
Is that how you check blood pressure?
I thought it was like a thing here.
Yeah, you can feel your pulse.
You didn't know that?
I'm fucking dead, because I can't find it.
Wait, is it the wrong side?
-I have work to do, lady!
-Go, go, go.
I can help you.
-You're gonna help me?
-Yeah.
-You're the best friend ever!
-I know.
Yeah, it's fine. I'm your best friend.
Davina's in here actually.
She heard everything you said.
Davina? Did you get that?
[Mary] You said you were gonna
brighten the place up.
[Jason] Chrishell, I'm sending you
a listing, an email.
That's the guy that does
a lot of business in the Valley.
Yeah, he kind of dominates.
He's our competition.
[Jason] We're gonna be
his competition soon.
Yes!
Hey, guys.
-[Mary] Hi.
-[Chrishell] That's cute.
-You look pretty.
-[Davina] Thank you. Hi.
[Heather] Jason, why am I under "Stanley"
show-- showing email?
-[Heather] He can't hear me.
-He sent that two days ago.
Wait, I just heard you.
[Heather] I know, exactly.
Been at the office for five years,
I'm in the back?
-[Heather laughing]
-You can sit on the couch.
Take it as a compliment.
[Heather] Amanza's been here how long?
Just saying.
[Jason] It goes by how long
I've known people.
So, my womb-mate, then my ex,
then my 20-year friend.
[Amanza] Did you say your "womb-mate"?
[Jason] My womb-mate.
I was here before her, before her...
[Mary] I've never heard you say that.
-Do you guys have plans this weekend?
-[Christine] What's going on?
I have a client
that has this awesome house
in Malibu on the beach
and so, I wanna have
a beach party in Malibu.
I wouldn't mind getting out of here
maybe on Friday.
Just do a fun day out in Malibu,
we'll go to Nobu
and go check out the house.
-[Christine] That'd be cool.
-[Amanza] Funday Friday?
[Jason] Yeah.
[Christine] Wait, so is it on the beach?
What's the attire?
-Obviously slut.
-[Heather] I mean, obviously.
[Amanza] There's like,
what we're gonna wear,
and then what Christine's gonna wear,
so I don't know.
-Beach casual?
-So what's the attire for you guys?
-[Christine] Vegas!
-Yeah.
-[Christine] Ready to go.
-You think you'll get eaten by a shark?
-Jason, can I talk to you for a sec?
-Yeah.
Okay.
So, um... you know I have
that client in Beverly Hills,
and you know, we looked at the property
and I've been talking to him,
communicating,
obviously he's a great client
and I want to impress him.
I mean, obviously, it would be like...
uh, an iconic listing, you know?
It would be amazing for me
and for you and the brokerage.
Please tell me he wants to give it to you.
He does want to give it to me.
Um... but we're, of course,
debating the price.
He's at, like, between 80 and 100 million,
so, yeah...
Oh, my God.
-I know. I know...
-That's just so overpriced that
we're just going to be spinning
our wheels spending money.
Do you know how much money?
I'm close to a 100,000 dollars
spent on the Hillside property right now.
[Jason] We split the marketing costs
with the agent, but we front those costs
and we get reimbursed when the property
sells and the agent make a commission.
So if the agent doesn't make a commission
because the property doesn't sell,
we're stuck with the marketing costs.
-All we need is one client, you know? One.
-No.
-Could be an international buyer...
-Now you sound like an unrealistic seller.
-"Oh, we just need one client."
-But we do.
That's almost embarrassing for us
to list it that high.
I don't think it's embarrassing.
What if we sat on the market for months
and got no showings?
-I agree with you.
-He's gonna think it's our fault.
Am I really not gonna try? Like...
That's like life-changing to me, you know?
But I'm more concerned that you're going
to just waste money. What about...
49 million?
[inhales sharply] I mean--
That's, like, a price I think
we can get behind.
But my point is, someone might offer 65.
-No one's offering 65.
-[Davina] How do you know?
-Because I know.
-Why can't I just try?
'Cause it's not a good look
for the brokerage.
What am I supposed to tell him?
"It's embarrassing?
Jason thinks it's embarrassing"?
I can't say that to the client.
It's a detriment to us
and it's a detriment to him.
He's gotta understand
it's not good for him either.
-Listen, Davina--
-I think you're being negative.
[Davina] It seems like Jason won't budge.
It's frustrating.
I mean, if I worked for myself,
I could just take the listing
and not have to worry about Jason.
How's this?
I'll think about it, and you tell him
it's worth 50 million,
and that he needs to get more realistic.
Otherwise, we're wasting his time.
I'm going to respectfully show him
the comps
and tell him your recommendation.
-Fine.
-And I'm gonna say let's talk about
how to best market this property
and the list price.
[Jason] Okay, fine.
[Heather] Tarek's birthday
is on Wednesday,
so I got him a Tumi travel case.
And he's obsessed with ChapStick
so I'm gonna get him a bunch of ChapStick.
[Amanza] Isn't that cute?
When's his birthday?
-[Heather] Wednesday.
-Oh.
[Heather] He's gonna be 38.
I texted his ex this morning
to touch base and...
-[Christine] Who?
-His ex.
[Heather] The ex-wife.
-[Christine] You have her number?
-He gave it to me to text her.
Really?
[Christine] Text her what?
[Heather] Because I'm around the kids,
so I wanted to introduce myself.
What?
[Christine] I gotta...
[Christine chuckles] I just had a moment.
I mean, why wouldn't I?
I'm just saying, as a mom,
as a person who went through it,
-that's a good thing.
-Exactly.
[Amanza] I haven't even met
my ex-husband's girlfriend.
My kids live with her.
And I'm like, I want--
We need to go to lunch.
-Exactly.
-She's helping raise my children.
[Heather] That's exactly what I said
to Tarek last night.
I will say though, it terrifies me
how fast you have met those kids.
-Because--
-[Heather] Why?
Because when and if something
doesn't work out,
-their hearts are crushed.
-Excuse me, when what doesn't work out?
[Amanza] It can happen.
I said, "When or if."
"When and if" is not gonna happen.
It's gonna work out.
We are very serious and...
going to move in together
and we're like moving forward
with everything.
So it's like.. I'd like to...
[Amanza] That's all fine and dandy.
I'm saying, I hope that you guys work out,
because if you break up,
those children are crushed.
I just went through it and it sucks.
It's like the hardest,
most heart-breaking thing.
I'm glad you're worried about
my boyfriend's children, thank you.
[Christine laughing]
[Heather] Thank you.
-Listen--
-[Heather] No, I do too, though.
If I thought you were going to be
this angry at me for saying it,
I would've kept my mouth shut.
-Good.
-I thought you knew me well enough to know
that I'm, like, not intentionally
bashing your relationship,
saying that you're a bad person,
saying that he's introduced
his, you know, kids to everybody.
I literally picked up on what you guys
were talking about and had a comment.
So I didn't feel like that was gonna cause
this huge negative reaction.
I care. I felt like sharing. Caring.
Thank you for your opinion,
I appreciate that.
Well, you don't.
Or else we wouldn't have had this...
-I actually don't, but thank you anyways.
-[Amanza] Then don't say you do.
That's... That's immature.
[Heather] Okay.
I just think people should mind
their own business. [scoffs]
♪ It's a good time
To let the madness play  ♪
♪ Dirty, dirty secret ♪
♪ My pretty lie... ♪
[Davina] It's always tough telling
a client their asking price is too high,
but it's part of the job.
So I just hope he can be reasonable.
[doorbell rings]
[Ece] Davina.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi.
-Great to see you.
-Thanks for having me.
[Ece] Adnan is here in the living room.
-Please, this way.
-Oh, great.
[clicking fingers]
Hi.
-Hi, how are you?
-Great to see you.
[Adnan] Welcome. Take a seat, please.
So, how is life? How is everything?
-It's good, it's good.
-Great.
Just trying to put a lot
of energy into work.
So, I obviously want to talk to you
about your listing, this property.
Um... I know we were talking
about sort of 80 million, the pricing...
I talked to Jason,
the owner of my brokerage, and...
he felt like 80 million
was very high for the area.
And he felt it was just kind
of a bit too aggressive.
And... I know...
[nervous laugh] I understand.
Um...
[Davina laughs nervously]
[laughing nervously]
So he, you know, he was telling me
that he felt it'd make
the brokers look bad
if we came on at a very high price.
He felt like he needed the pricing
to be at 60 million.
I know, I don't agree with that.
Um... I know that
that's not going to work. Um...
So I don't know if you would consider
any kind of lower number
or if we can talk
about anything like that.
Sixty is out of question.
-Yeah...
-[Adnan] First of all, the realtors,
they always get the same answer, right?
"Let's take the price down."
-I understand.
-But really,
you should increase the price, right?
I mean it took years to build
our reputation and image.
Yeah.
We are not just building
20,000 square-foot mansions.
They are not cheap.
Um...
But I'm having to deal
with Jason, my brokerage,
who's not willing to take it over 60.
So...
Honey, you know that
we have a lot of realtors...
-Yeah, absolutely.
-...who we are in contact with
as we are continuously building.
You or Jason might want
to have something cheaper,
there are lots of them on the market,
but if you really want something good,
that costs, baby.
No, I'm very well aware. I mean,
I think it does command more than 50,
60 million, of the properties in the area.
I think we can go 70 maybe, but...
Honey, I don't like you
negotiating with me.
You should be negotiating
with the clients, not with me.
-Absolutely. Yes, sir.
-You should be getting the best price.
Um...
This is a huge opportunity for me.
It's the most expensive listing
I would ever have.
And I'm so grateful
that you're considering me.
You know, I have clients and contacts
and other agents that I know
that may have buyers for this.
So... I think I could generate a buyer
closer to 80 as an offer.
Fine. We will work with you,
but I want you to perform.
I don't want only fancy words
-and all this stuff.
-I understand.
And we'll make a deal
with you for three months.
-Okay.
-Only three months this project.
Okay, so let her have that for 75.
[Davina] Okay. Thank you so much Adnan,
I appreciate it.
[Adnan] Congratulations.
I'm not going to let you down.
Thank you very much.